<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Martyn Taylor</title>
    <link href="https://martyntaylor.com/blog" />
    <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="https://martyntaylor.com/blog/feed.atom" />
    <updated>2021-02-24T12:42:08+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://martyntaylor.com/blog/feed.atom</id>
    <author>
        <name>Martyn Taylor</name>
    </author>
                <entry>
    <id>https://martyntaylor.com/blog/done-is-better-than-perfect</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="https://martyntaylor.com/blog/done-is-better-than-perfect" />
    <title>Done is better than perfect</title>
    <published>2021-02-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Martyn</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">Introduction to my long overdue blog....</summary>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
        <p>So here it is.</p>

<p>After years of procrastination, I have finally launched my site.</p>

<p>It's not how I imagined it would look.</p>

<p>I have developed this site many, many times. I just never published it as I would always end up unhappy with the outcome. Not that these sites were bad, it was more me chasing my version of perfection that I could never manage.</p>

<p>This form of perfection procrastination has hindered me not only in my quest to get this site produced, but in many aspects of my life (even now as I write, and rewrite this post).</p>

<p>As this is something I want to improve on, I had a reminder earlier today when my manager at Car &amp; Classic posted this tweet in our Slack channel -</p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">“First do it, then do it right, then do it better.”<br>― Addy Osmani</p>&mdash; Amir Salihefendić (@amix3k) <a href="https://twitter.com/amix3k/status/1359774458244866050?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 11, 2021</a></blockquote>

<script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>

<p>What if I just get something up?</p>

<p>After all this is what I do in my job. We work to produce an MVP, then iterate over making improvements, so why am I not following this for my own site?</p>

<p>With renewed motivation, I decided on a static site generator - <a href="https://jigsaw.tighten.co/" title="" rel="nofollow" target="blank">Jigsaw</a> from Tighten which is aimed at Laravel developers.</p>

<p>With the aim to getting something up, I tried not to be precious about the design.  In fact, it is a stripped down version of their starter theme, with just a different font and default colour.</p>

<p>Sure it's not the <em>best</em> looking site, but I  will improve upon this (along with my writing!), but for now its up and out there for the world to see.</p>

<p>I hope you enjoy :)</p>
    ]]></content>
</entry>
    </feed>
